# 哈喽 大家好
Hello
# 今天我就放个假做一桌菜
I’m taking a break today and cooking a meal
# 大家一家人聚到一起
The whole family gather here
# 其实平时我老爸老妈跟我哥他们都在
Actually my parent and my brother are usually around
# 只是他们不喜欢上镜而已
They just don’t like being on camera
# 然后今天都上镜了
And they are all on camera today
# 因为我们家小宝宝满100天
Because it’s the 100th day since my baby was born
# 因为他满月的时候因为疫情嘛
When he was one month old
# 所以也没有给他摆个酒什么的
We didn’t celebrate because of the outbreak
# 今天简简单单的我们一家人吃个饭
Today, my whole family is going to eat together (to celebrate)
# 来嘛 吃
Come on, let’s eat
# 来来来
Come on
# 来 干杯
Come on, Cheers!
# 我要吃多宝鱼
I want to eat turbot
# 吃多宝鱼啊 来爸爸给你夹
You want turbot? Let me help you with that
# 你帮我夹个菜菜幺儿
Can you help me get some of that dish, Yao er
# 人家家用大碗喝
They use big bowls for drinking
# 还喝酒
Drink alcohol?
# 来来来喝点酒
Come on, let’s drink some
# 哦哟 这白酒哦 喝得不哦
Oh this is Baijiu? I can’t handle it
# 喝酒喝酒
Let’s drink
# 干杯干杯
Cheers
# 那个酒没得味道的
That Baijiu doesn’t taste like alcohol
# 来嘛 我们来喝一个
Come on, raise your drinks
# 好不容易一起来上镜的
Finally you are all on camera
# 你们平时都不上镜
You don’t usually on camera
# 来嘛来嘛
Come on
# 干杯干杯
Cheers
# 来干杯
# 要干哈
Need to drink it all
# 人家是水
That’s water
# 慢点哦
Eat slowly